哇！那里正在下猫和狗（双关：正在下大雨）！
Whoa! It's raining cats and dogs out there!
我希望他们能回来做好
I hope they make it back all right.
小心！安迪来了！
Heads up! Andy's coming!
安迪 晚餐时间
Andy, time for dinner.
是!我饿死了！
Yes! I'm starving!
别忘了洗手！
Don't forget to wash your hands!
好的 妈妈！
Okay, Mom!
- 你看到他了吗？ - 没有
- Do you see him? - No.
好吧 他已经完成了
Well, he's done for.
他会迷路的！永远！
He'll be lost! Forever!
杰西 嗡嗡声 早产 莫莉的房间
Jessie. Buzz. Slink. Molly's room.
其他人 留下来
The rest of you, stay put.
博！
Bo!
情况？
Situation?
丢失的玩具 边院
Lost toy. Side yard.
比利 山羊 粗暴 提高百叶窗
Billy. Goat. Gruff. Raise the blinds.
他们有名字？你从来没有告诉过我
They have names? You never told me that.
你从未问过
You never asked.
他在哪里？
Where is he?
那里！
There!
我们怎么联系他？
How do we reach him?
操作拉玩具！
Operation Pull-Toy!
Operation Pull
-Toy!
早产！你知道了 温迪！
Operation Pull-Toy!
Slink! You got it, Woody!
芭比娃娃！
Barbies!
走！
Go!
手电筒
Flashlight.
坚持下去 R.C ！
Hang on, R.C.!
我没有更多的眨眼！
I ain't got any more slink!
哦 它很漂亮
Oh, it's beautiful.
我很高兴看到
I'm so glad to see
这个旧灯去了一个好家
this old lamp go to a good home.
我们已经拥有它 因为莫莉还是个孩子
We've had it since Molly was a baby.
莫莉 你确定没事吗？
Molly, are you sure it's all right?
是的 我不再想要了
Yeah, I don't want it anymore.
谢谢
Thank you.
温迪在哪里？
Where's Woody?
是的 嗨 我想我把钥匙留在了这里
Yeah, hi. I think I left my keys here.
温迪 快！
Woody. Quick!
在他回来之前我们会潜入树篱
We'll sneak in the hedges before he's back.
温迪 没关系
Woody, it's okay.
什么不！不不不 你不能去！
What No! No, no, no. You can't go!
对安迪最好的是......温迪
What's best for Andy is that... Woody.
我不是安迪的玩具
I'm not Andy's toy.
什么？
What?
现在是下一个孩子的时候了
It's time for the next kid.
哦 再次感谢你的一切
Oh, and thank you again for everything.
我真的很感激
I really appreciate it.
哦 我很高兴 我很高兴这一切都成功了
Oh, my pleasure. I'm glad it all worked out.
你知道 孩子们每天都会失去玩具
You know, kids lose their toys every day.
有时他们会离开院子......
Sometimes they get left in the yard...
或放入错误的方框
or put in the wrong box.
那个盒子被拿走了
And that box gets taken away.
妈妈 温迪在哪里？
Mom, where's Woody?
安迪！请你进来！
Andy! Come inside!
我找不到温迪！
I can't find Woody!
那晚安啦
Well, good night.
再见 安全驾驶
Goodbye. Drive safe.
哦 你在这儿
Oh, there you are.
妈妈 我找到了他！我找到他了！
Mom, I found him! I found him!
哦 好的 来吧 进去吧
Oh, good. Come on and get inside.
你有一个朋友在我身边
You've got a friend in me.
伸手去拿天空！
Reach for the sky!
你有一个朋友在我身边
You've got a friend in me.
骑他们 牛仔！绮山楂！
Ride 'em, cowboy! Yee-haw!
当道路前方看起来粗糙时
When the road looks rough ahead.
我的靴子里有一条蛇
There's a snake in my boot.
而且距离你温暖的床还有几英里
And you're miles and miles From your nice warm bed
你只记得你的老朋友说的话
You just remember what your old pal said
男孩 你有一个朋友
Boy, you've got a friend in me.
超越无限！
To infinity and beyond!
是的 你有一个朋友在我身边
Yeah, you've got a friend in me.
我的牛仔！
My cowboy!
现在 其他一些人可能比我更聪明一些
Now, some other folks might be a little bit smarter than I am
又大又强 温迪 我们走吧！
Big and stronger, too Woody, let's go!
也许吧
Maybe
但他们中没有人会像我一样爱你
But none of them will ever love you the way I do.
你是我最喜欢的副手！
You're my favorite deputy!
这是我和你 男孩
It's me and you, boy
随着岁月的流逝
And as the years go by
我们的友谊永远不会消亡
Our friendship will never die.
伸手去拿天空！
Reach for the sky!
你会发现这是我们的命运
You're gonna see it's our destiny.
他们逃脱了 他们正朝着我们前进！
They've escaped and they're headed right for us!
你有一个朋友在我身边
You've got a friend in me.
全速前进！好极了！你已经赢得了我这个朋友
Full speed ahead! Yay! You've got a friend in me
你有一个朋友在我身边
You've got a friend in me
它在这里越来越热了！
It's getting hot in here!
我的耳朵在哪里？
Where's my ear?
你站起来了！
You're on my foot!
哦 嘿 不要再推了推
Oh, hey, quit shoving.
- 抱歉！ - 你能过来吗？
- Sorry! - Could you move over
- 好吗？ - 那是我的号角
- a bit, please? - That was my horn.
超越无限！
To infinity and beyond!
我知道那是你 马铃薯头
I know that was you, Potato Head.
大家 听 我以为我告诉过你了......
Everyone, listen. I thought I told you...
当妈妈像那样迅速清理卧室时......
when Mom quickly cleans the bedroom like that...
期待被放入壁橱
expect to be put in the closet.
多久了？
How much longer?
雷克斯 让它保持沉闷的咆哮
Keep it to a dull roar, Rex.
深呼吸 杰西 深呼吸
Deep breaths, Jessie. Deep breaths.
定居下来 斯林克
Settle down, Slink.
坐 好孩子！
Sit. Good boy!
警长 我需要担心吗？
Sheriff, do I need to be worried?
不 不 我的家伙都是退伍军人 他们会挂在那里
No, no. My guys are veterans. They'll hang in there.
好 让我们保持冷静 直到我们得到消息
Good. Just keep them calm until we get word.
是的女士
Yes, ma'am.
你今天感觉怎么样？
How are you, uh, feeling about today?
呃 好 好 耶 好样的
Uh, good, good. Yeah, good.
我很好
I'm good.
呃......很好
Uh... Good.
我们在！邦妮完成了早餐！
We're on! Bonnie's done with breakfast!
现在任何一分钟 你听到了吗？
Any minute now. You hear that?
现在任何一分钟
Any minute now.
如果你有他们的话 风吧
Wind 'em if you got 'em.
保持电池清洁 关节解锁......
Keep your batteries clean, your joints unlocked...
呃 谢谢 温迪 我知道了
Uh, thanks, Woody. I got it.
是的 对不起 你是对的 你是对的
Yes, I'm sorry. You're right, you're right.
小镇开放！
The town is open!
嗨 市长！
Hi, Mayor!
银行家！
Banker!
嗨 冰淇淋男！嗨 帽店老板！
Hi, Ice-Cream Man! Hi, Hat Shop Owner!
邮差！
Mailman!
和治安官！
And the sheriff!
好的 再见 玩具！
Okay. Bye, toys!
绮山楂！警长杰西！
Yee-haw! Sheriff Jessie!
头晕 舷窗！
Giddy-up, Bullseye!
他们走那条路！
They went that way!
追他们！
Chase them!
多么漂亮的帽子店！你有这么多帽子......
What a beautiful hat shop! You have so many hats...
哇 他们正在做“帽店”
Wow. They're doing "hat shop."
什么时候是最后一次
When's the last time
我们有没有玩过那个？
we ever got to play that?
还记得她玩“房子”吗？
Remember when she played "house"?
我喜欢“房子”
I liked "house."
那些日子
Those were the days.
这是基本的 你做了一所房子
It was basic. You made a house,
你住在里面 完成了
you lived in it, done.
嗯 这是第三次
Hmm. That's the third time
你本周没有被选中
you haven't been picked this week.
我不知道 我不记得了
I don't know. I don't keep count.
哦 你不必
Oh, you don't have to.
我会帮你的 好的 好的 我明白了
I'll do it for you. Okay, okay, okay, I get it.
有一阵子了
It's been a while.
哦 看那里
Oh, looky there.
你有第一个尘土兔子
You got your first dust bunny.
噢 多么可爱
Aw, how adorable.
你会说出什么名字？
What you gonna name it?
呃 达斯迪怎么样？
Uh, what about Dusty?
- 弗朗西斯！ - 哈利！
- Francis! - Harry!
- 凯伦！ -  发兹宝！
- Karen! - Fuzzball!
勒布朗不 蓬松
LeBron No, Fluffy.
-  桑普怎么样？ - 风滚草！
- How about Thumper? - Tumbleweed!
“风滚草” 哦 这是个好 那很好
"Tumbleweed." Oh, that's good. That's good.
他是个牛仔
He's a cowboy,
所以这很有道理
so that makes a lot of sense.
这么多的选择
So many choices.
我只是无法决定！
I just can't decide!
邦妮？
Bonnie?
你在做什么？我们走了
What are you doing? We got to go.
你不想迟到
You don't wanna be late
对于幼儿园的定位 你呢？
for kindergarten orientation, do you?
但我不想去
But I don't wanna go.
我们谈到了这一点
We talked about this.
我们要去见你的老师
We're gonna meet your teachers,
看你的教室......我可以带玩具吗？
see your classroom... Can I bring a toy?
玩具不上学 这是规则
Toys don't go to school, that's the rule.
冻结！没有人动！
Freeze! Nobody move!
邦妮总是忘记一些事情
Bonnie always forgets something.
她会在任何时候回来
She'll be back any second.
这也适合你 哈姆
That goes for you, too, Hamm.
但这是钱！
But it's money!
你好吗 温迪？
You all right, Woody?
我相信她下次会接你的
I'm sure she'll pick you next time.
哦 来吧 我很好 没问题
Oh, come on, I'm fine. No problem.
嘿 温迪 这里
Hey, Woody. Here.
哦 谢谢 杰西
Oh, thanks, Jessie.
哥们 我们在这里等你
We're here for you, buddy.
但邦妮不是安迪
不 不 不 当然 我明白了
但如果你只是......地方 大家！
我不想扮演面包师
I don't want to play the baker.
刺绣裤子
Pricklepants.
帽店老板是我出生的角色！
The hat shop owner is the role I was born to play!
好吧 刺绣裤子 回到你的面包店
All right, Pricklepants, back to your bakery.
对不起 多莉？
Excuse me, Dolly?
温迪 难道你不能看到我威胁每个人吗？
Woody, can't you see I'm threatening everyone?
回到壁橱里
Go back to the closet.
我很担心邦妮
I'm worried about Bonnie.
玩具应该和她一起去定位
A toy should go with her to orientation.
你没听见爸爸吗？你会让邦妮陷入困境
Didn't you hear Dad? You'll get Bonnie in trouble.
是的 但幼儿园是如此不同
Yeah, but kindergarten is so different.
这对孩子来说太过分了
It can be too much for a kid.
与他们的伙伴通过它
Having a buddy with them to get through it
真的可以帮助你
can really help things.
嗯 对不起 温迪
Uh-huh. I'm sorry, Woody,
but Bonnie's not Andy.
No, no, no, of course, I get that.
But if you would just...
Places, everyone!
邦妮？
Bonnie?
那你在做什么？
What are you doing back there?
来吧 我们得走了
Come on, we have to go.
那是我的大姑娘
That's my big girl.
来吧 我们快点 好吗？
Come on. We got to hurry, okay?
别忘了你的背包
Don't forget your backpack.
你会有这么多的乐趣
You're gonna have so much fun.
好吧 现在你说的是什么 温迪？
All right. Now what was it you were saying, Woody?
温迪？
Woody?
我们来了
Here we are.
邦妮 亲爱的 没关系
Bonnie, honey, it'll be okay.
嗨！你是邦妮吗？
Hi! Are you Bonnie?
我叫温迪小姐
My name is Miss Wendy.
我将成为你的幼儿园老师
I'm going to be your kindergarten teacher.
我们有一个特殊的地方 你可以把你的背包
We have a special place where you can put your backpack.
你想看？
You want to see?
我们在这里 邦妮 只为你
Here we are, Bonnie. Just for you.
好的 上课 让我们都在桌子上找个座位......
Okay, class, let's all find a seat at a table...
所以我们可以开始工艺时间
so we can start craft time.
在上学的第一天
On the first day of school,
你需要一个放置铅笔的地方
you'll need a place to put your pencils.
所以 今天 我们要制作铅笔夹
So, today, we're going to make pencil holders.
现在 每个人都拿一杯......
Now, everyone take a cup...
我们将使用艺术品来装饰它们
and we'll use the art supplies to decorate them.
你好
Hi.
邦妮 那太聪明了
Bonnie. That is so clever.
“你好 我是叉子 很高兴见到你！”
"Hello, I'm Forky. Nice to meet you!"
好吧 你好 叉子 很高兴见到你
Well, hello, Forky, it's nice to meet you.
我是温迪小姐
I'm Miss Wendy.
妈妈！爸！看看我做了什么！
Mom! Dad! Look what I made!
他的名字叫叉子！
His name is Forky!
哇！真是太酷了！
Wow! That is so cool!
我完成了幼儿园！
I finished kindergarten!
呃......不 那只是方向
Uh... No. That was just orientation.
但对于这样一个勇敢的女孩
But for being such a brave girl,
我们给你一个惊喜
we have a surprise for you.
它是什么？
What is it?
由于学校没有开始
Since school doesn't start
再过一周 我们正在进行一次公路旅行！
for another week, we are going on a road trip!
- 我可以带叉子吗？ - '当然可以！
- Can I bring Forky? - 'Course you can!
好极了！
Yay!
他们说我不应该和邦妮上学
And they said I shouldn't go to school with Bonnie.
我们把幼儿园的事情控制住了 是吗？
We got this kindergarten thing under control, eh?
我简直不敢相信我正在和一个叉勺说话
I can't believe I'm talking to a spork.
嗨 玩具！再见 玩具！
Hi, toys! Bye, toys!
噢
Ow.
他确实去了幼儿园！
He did go to kindergarten!
我就知道 不 不 不 伙计们 听......
I knew it. No, no, no, guys, listen...
你试着让邦妮陷入困境吗？
You tryin' to get Bonnie in trouble?
不 当然不！
No, of course not!
你可能被没收了
You could have been confiscated.
这意味着什么？
What does that mean Taken away.
没有！或者更糟
No! Or worse.
你可能已经迷路了！
You could've been lost!
不 不 不 伙计们 听
No, no, no, guys, listen.
邦妮在课堂上度过了美好的一天......
Bonnie had a great day in class...
我们要去公路旅行
and we're going on a road trip.
公路旅行度假！
Road trip Vacation!
绮山楂！
Yee-haw!
但后来发生了一些非常奇怪的事情
But then something really weird happened.
邦妮在课堂上结识了一位朋友
Bonnie made a friend in class.
真是个孩子
What a kid.
哦 她已经结交了朋友
Oh, she's already making friends.
不 不 她真的成了一个新朋友
No, no. She literally made a new friend.
嘿 没关系
Hey, it's okay.
来吧而已
Come on out. That's it.
来吧 你去吧
Come on, there you go.
来吧 让我们离开那里
Come on, let's get you out of there.
你有这个
You got this.
好 好
Good. Good.
大家好 我想让你见到叉子
Everyone, I want you to meet Forky.
-  奥利·鲍勃你好！ - 看那个！
- Golly bob howdy! - Look at that!
看看他的手臂有多长！
Look how long his arms are!
垃圾号
Trash No.
不 玩具
No, toys.
他们都是玩具
They're all toys.
垃圾不 不 不
Trash No, no, no.
那是垃圾
That's the trash.
这些是你的朋友
These are your friends.
嗨！
Hi!
垃圾！
Trash!
不 不 没关系 垃圾！
No, no, it's okay. Trash!
温迪 我有一个问题
Woody, I have a question.
嗯 实际上 不只是一个
Um, well, actually, not just one,
我拥有所有这些
I have all of them.
我有所有的问题
I have all the questions.
呃 他为什么要去垃圾桶？
Uh, why does he want to go to the trash?
因为他是用垃圾做的
Because he was made from trash.
垃圾！
Trash!
看 我知道这有点奇怪
Look, I know this is a little strange,
但是你必须相信我
but you got to trust me on this.
垃圾？
Trash?
叉子现在是邦妮最重要的玩具
Forky is the most important toy to Bonnie right now.
重要？
Important?
他是个笨蛋
He's a spork.
是 是的 我知道 但这个叉勺 ......
Yes. Yeah, I know, but this spork...
这个玩具对邦妮至关重要
this toy is crucial to Bonnie
适应幼儿园 哦
getting adjusted to kindergarten. Oh.
温迪 你不是吗？
Woody, aren't you being
关于这一切有点戏剧性？
a little dramatic about all this?
我知道这对每个人都是新的......
I know this is new to everybody...
但你应该看多少
but you should see how much
this little guy means to Bonnie.
这个小家伙意味着邦妮
当她开始和他一起玩的时候......
When she started playing with him...
她的脸上露出了最大的笑容
she had the biggest smile on her face.
我希望你能看到它
I wish you could have seen it.
邦妮真的很不高兴......
Bonnie was really upset...
我发誓 一旦她做了叉子......
and I swear, once she made Forky...
这是一次彻底的转变
it was a complete transformation.
呃 温迪？一秒钟 杰西
Uh, Woody? Just a second, Jessie.
所以 我们都必须确保没有任何事情发生在他身上
So, we all have to make sure nothing happens to him.
他身上发生了一些事
Something happened to him.
哦 滑道和梯子！
Oh, Chutes and Ladders!
啊 垃圾
Ah, trash.
- 不不不！ - 不！没有！
- No, no, no! - No! No!
- 你现在是个玩具 叉子！ - 来吧！
- You're a toy now, Forky! - Come on!
停止！停下来！
Stop! Stop it!
- 嘿！不不不！来吧！ - 垃圾！
- Hey! No, no, no! Come on! - Trash!
垃圾！垃圾！
Trash! Trash!
好吧 我想我只是照顾他
Well, I guess I'll just babysit him
直到他习惯了房间
till he's used to the room.
嗯
Hmm.
的叉子？
Forky?
你在哪儿 叉子？
Where are you, Forky?
你在这！
There you are!
我以为我会失去你 傻
I thought I'd lost you, silly.
不不不 大女孩吓人！
No, no, no. Big girl scary!
就像我之前说过的那样 邦妮并不可怕
Like I said before, Bonnie's not scary.
她爱你 你需要...哦
She loves you and you need to... Ooh.
的叉子？
Forky?
邦尼！
Bonnie!
我们走吧！
Let's go!
兴高采烈！
Rise and shine!
谁想去公路旅行？
Who wants to go on a road trip?
我！我要带多莉 还有毛茛......
Me! I'm gonna bring Dolly, and Buttercup...
和叉子 和...叉子你在哪里？
and Forky, and... Forky Where are you?
他必须在某个地方
He's got to be here somewhere.
的叉子？
Forky?
的叉子！
Forky!
来吧 我们吃一些早餐然后上路吧！
Come on. Let's eat some breakfast and hit the road!
我们走了 叉子！
Let's go, Forky!
哇 他很少 温迪
Whoa. He's quite a handful, Woody.
你在公路旅行中需要帮助吗？
You need help with him on the road trip?
不不不 我明白了 我明白了
No. No, no. I got it, I got it.
我们只会陷入房车
We'll just be stuck in an RV.
他无法走远 我懂了
He can't get far. I got this.
我知道了
I got it.
我不能让你？我不能让你
I can't let you? I can't let you
我不能让你把自己扔掉
I can't let you throw yourself away
我不能让你？我不能让你
I can't let you? I can't let you
我不能让你把自己扔掉
I can't let you throw yourself away.
你不想每天早晨看到太阳升起吗？
Don't you want to see the sun come up each morning
不 不！
No, no!
你不想每天都看到太阳下山吗？
Don't you want to see the sun go down each day
你不想看到那个爱你的小女孩吗？
Don't you want to see that little girl that loves you so
她的心会破碎哦 是的！
Her heart would break Oh, yeah!
如果你应该去
If you should go
我不能让你？我不能让你
I can't let you? I can't let you
我不能让你把自己扔掉
I can't let you throw yourself away.
不不不！
No, no, no!
没有！没有！没有！
No! No! No!
所以在我看来 你似乎永远不会表现自己
So it seems to me like you're never gonna behave yourself
因为我不会每天都这样做
Since I'm not gonna do this every day
明天来 你必须要自救
Come tomorrow, you're gonna have to save yourself
无话可说
Got nothing more to say
无论如何你不是在听
You're not listening anyway
我不能让你？我不能让你
I can't let you? I can't let you.
垃圾 我来了！
Trash, here I come!
我不能让你把自己扔掉
I can't let you throw yourself away.
来吧
Come on.
我不能让你？我不能让你
I can't let you? I can't let you
我不能让你把自己扔掉
I can't let you throw yourself away
我不想成为一个玩具！
I don't wanna be a toy!
我不能让你？我不能让你
I can't let you? I can't let you
我不能让你把自己扔掉
I can't let you throw yourself away
你好朋友
Hey, buddy.
嘿 巴兹
Hey, Buzz.
你还好吗？
You doing okay?
我不知道 巴兹
I don't know, Buzz.
当安迪很小的时候我知道你不在身边......
I know you weren't around when Andy was little...
但我不记得这很难
but I don't remember it being this hard.
想让我拍下一块手表吗？
Want me to take the next watch?
我会留意叉子
I'll keep an eye on Forky.
不 不 我需要这样做
No, no. I need to do this.
我内心的那个小声音
That little voice inside me
如果我放弃 我永远不会离开我
would never leave me alone if I gave up.
呵呵
Huh.
你认为它是谁？
Who do you think it is?
谁？
Who?
你内心的声音 你认为它是谁？
The voice inside of you. Who do you think it is?
呃......我
Uh... Me.
你知道 我的良心？
You know, my conscience?
那部分你告诉你的事情？
That part of you that tells you things?
你在想什么？
What you're really thinking?
迷人
Fascinating.
所以 你内心的声音建议你
So, your inner voice advises you.
什么？
What?
这是未知空间的秘密任务
It's a secret mission in uncharted space.
我们走吧
Let's go.
什么是叉子？
Where's Forky?
不好了！的叉子！
Oh, no! Forky!
的叉子！
Forky!
我不是玩具！
I am not a toy!
我是个笨蛋
I'm a spork.
安静！
Be quiet!
我是为汤 沙拉做的...
I was made for soup, salad...
也许是辣椒 然后是垃圾
maybe chili, and then the trash.
我乱扔垃圾！
I'm litter!
自由！
Freedom!
哈姆 我们下一站有多远？
Hamm, how far to our next stop?
5.32英里 给予或接受
我可以做到这一点
I can make that.
我会在RV公园见到你
I'll meet you at the RV park.
温迪 等一下 温迪！
Woody, hold on a minute. Woody!
的叉子！
Forky!
叉子 你在哪里？
Forky, where are you?
的叉子！
Forky!
叉子 你在哪里？
Forky, where are you?
给我带号
Carry me No.
为什么我必须成为一个玩具？
Why do I have to be a toy?
因为你有邦妮的名字
Because you have Bonnie's name
写在你的棍棒底部
written on the bottom of your sticks.
为什么我有邦妮的名字
Why do I have Bonnie's name
写在我的棍棒底部？
written on the bottom of my sticks?
因为她...
Because she...
看 她一直和你一起玩 对吧？
Look, she plays with you all the time, right?
啊 是
Ugh. Yes.
她每晚都和谁睡觉？
And who does she sleep with every night?
大白蓬松的东西？
The big white fluffy thing?
不 不是她的枕头
No, not her pillow.
您
You.
好吧 叉子
All right, Forky.
你必须明白你现在有多幸运
You have to understand how lucky you are right now.
你是邦妮的玩具
You're Bonnie's toy.
你将帮助创造美好的回忆......
You are going to help create happy memories...
这将持续余生
that will last for the rest of her life.
啊 啥？
Huh, What?
好的 为邦妮做这件事
Okay. Doing it for Bonnie.
Doing this for Bonnie, you're doing it for Bonnie.
Doing this for Bonnie,
you're doing it for Bonnie.
为邦妮这样做 你是为邦妮做的
Doing this for Bonnie, you're doing it for Bonnie.
好吧 无论喜欢与否 你都是一个玩具
Okay, like it or not, you are a toy.
也许你不喜欢成为一个
Maybe you don't like being one,
但你仍然是一个人
but you are one nonetheless.
这意味着你要去
Which means you are going
安迪出现在那里......谁是安迪？
to be there for Andy when he... Who's Andy?
我的意思是 邦妮
I mean, Bonnie.
你必须在那里为邦妮
You have to be there for Bonnie.
那是你的工作
That is your job.
嗯 你的工作是什么？
Well, what's your job?
那么 现在 这是为了确保你做你的
Well, right now, it's to make sure you do yours.
抱我不！
Carry me No!
谁是安迪？
Who's Andy?
安迪是我的另一个孩子
Andy was my other kid.
你有另一个孩子？
You had another kid?
是啊
Yeah, yeah.
需很长时间
For a long time.
它非常棒
And it was pretty great.
实际上 我是最喜欢的玩具
I was a favorite toy, actually.
经营房间是我的工作
Running the room was my job.
保持所有玩具到位......
Keeping all the toys in place...
所以 他认为安迪的房间是一个星球？
So, he thought Andy's room was a planet?
哇 这搞砸了
Wow, that is messed up.
对！
Right!
这正是我第一次出现时的想法
That's exactly what I thought when he first showed up.
Yeah. I mean, how is that not annoying?
是啊 我的意思是 这怎么不烦人？
谢谢！说真的 就是......
Thank you! Seriously, that is the...
那么 你看着他们长大了
Well, then you watch 'em grow up
并成为一个完整的人
and become a full person.
然后他们离开了
And then they leave.
他们走了 做你永远不会看到的事情
They go off and do things you'll never see.
不要误会我的意思 你仍然感觉很好
Don't get me wrong, you still feel good about it.
但是不知怎的 你发现自己
But then somehow you find yourself,
经过那么多年......
after all those years...
坐在壁橱​​里感觉......
sitting in a closet just feeling...
无用？
Useless?
是啊
Yeah.
你的目的实现了吗？
Your purpose fulfilled?
究竟
Exactly.
温迪 我知道你的问题是什么
Woody, I know what your problem is.
你做？
You do?
你就像我一样
You're just like me.
垃圾！
Trash!
什么是你和垃圾？
What is it with you and trash?
很温暖  嗯
It's warm. Ew.
这很舒适 我猜
It's cozy. I guess.
而且安全！
And safe!
就像有人在你耳边低语
Like somebody's whispering in your ear,
“一切都会好的 ”
"Everything's gonna be okay."
叉子 就是这样
Forky, that's it.
这就是邦妮和你在一起时的感受
That's how Bonnie feels when she's with you.
她做的是！
She does Yes!
等一下
Wait a sec.
你的意思是她认为我很温暖？是的
You mean she thinks I'm warm? Yep.
惬意嗯嗯
And cozy Uh-huh.
有时候有点软弱？
And sometimes kinda squishy?
嗯 那也是 是
Well, that, too. Yes.
我现在明白了
I get it now.
我是邦妮的垃圾
I'm Bonnie's trash.
是!等等 什么？
Yes! Wait, what?
我是邦妮的垃圾！
I am Bonnie's trash!
不 不 不 不完全是
No, no, no, not exactly.
没有我 她一定感觉很糟糕
She must be feeling awful without me.
温迪 我们得走了 她需要我！
Woody, we got to get going, she needs me!
是啊...哇 哇 嘿 邦妮 我来了！
Yeah... Whoa, whoa. Hey, Bonnie, I'm coming!
叉子 慢下来！的叉子！
Forky, slow down! Forky!
邦妮 我来了！
Bonnie, I'm coming!
的叉子！
Forky!
叉子 看 邦妮就在那边
Forky, look. Bonnie's right over there.
匆忙！
Hurry!
喔！
Whoo!
嗯温迪？
Huh Woody?
博？
Bo?
温迪？
Woody?
我们不是要去邦妮吗？
Aren't we going to Bonnie?
我知道我知道 但我的朋友可能在那里
I know, I know. But my friend might be in there.
朋友？
Friend?
哦 朋友 呃......好吧 朋友是......
Oh, a friend, uh... Well, a friend is...
好吧 朋友就像你我一样
Well, a friend is like you and me.
垃圾垃圾 就像......是的
Trash Trash, like... Yes.
而且我很担心她可能会迷路
And I'm very worried that she might be lost.
但是 温迪 邦妮就在那里
But, Woody, Bonnie's right there.
是的 我们会在她醒来之前让你回来 来吧
Yeah, we'll have you back before she wakes up. Come on.
博？
Bo?
博波？
Bo Bo?
博？
Bo?
博
Bo.
博 博 博 ......
Bo, Bo, Bo...
博波？
Bo Bo?
我们现在可以回到邦妮吗？
Can we go back to Bonnie now?
我没有看到你的朋友
I don't see your friend.
好的
Yeah, okay.
她不在这里
She's not in here.
来吧 我们走吧
Come on, let's go.
是博？
Is that Bo?
呃......嘿 你好
Uh... Hey, howdy.
嘿
Hey there.
呃 很抱歉打扰你 但......
Uh, sorry to bother you, but...
为什么 你根本不是一个麻烦
Why, you're not a bother at all.
我们刚刚出去散步
We were just out for my early morning stroll.
看......我们遇到了你！
And look... we met you!
我叫加比·加比
My name is Gabby Gabby.
这是我非常好的朋友本森
And this is my very good friend Benson.
哦 呃 温迪 很高兴认识你
Oh, uh, Woody. Pleasure to meet you.
温迪 很高兴见到你 你是......？
Well, it's nice to meet you, Woody. And you are...?
这是叉子
This is Forky.
我很垃圾
I'm trash.
我们的孩子让他
Our kid made him.
这里的儿童玩具没有孩子
Kid Toys around here don't have kids.
你们两个迷路了？
Are you two lost?
丢了不 不
Lost No, no.
但我们正在寻找丢失的玩具
But we are looking for a lost toy.
她是个小雕像 曾经在窗户上的那盏灯上吗？
She's a figurine. Used to be on that lamp in the window?
名字叫博皮？
Name's Bo Peep?
博皮？
Bo Peep?
哦 是的 我知道博 你做？
Oh, yes, I know Bo. You do?
继续 我们会带你去她
Hop on in. We'll take you to her.
哦 你不必这样做
Oh, you don't have to do that.
哦 那好吧
Well, okay.
本森 小心我们的新朋友
Benson, be careful with our new friends.
哇 什么服务
Wow, what service.
呃...谢谢你的帮助
Uh... Thank you for your help.
我好几年没见过博
I haven't seen Bo in years.
请问 你什么时候做的？
May I ask, when were you made?
我呃......
Me Uh...
我不确定  50年代末期？
I'm not sure. Late '50s?
我也是！
Me, too!
哎呀 我想知道我们是不是在同一家工厂生产的
Gee, I wonder if we were made in the same factory.
那不是什么事吗？
Wouldn't that be something?
我得说 你状况很好
I got to say, you are in great condition.
好吧 我尽力保持活跃
Well, I try to stay active.
看看那个
And look at that,
你有像我这样的语音盒
you have a voice box like me.
本森 告诉他
Benson, show him.
哦 那真的没必要
Oh, that's really not necessary.
我是加比·加比
I'm Gabby Gabby
我爱你
and I love you.
哇 你需要解决这个问题
Wow, you need to fix that.
我的录音很好
My record works just fine.
这是语音盒坏了
It's the voice box that's broken.
你的还活着吗？
Does yours still work?
嘿!
Hey!
我的靴子里有一条蛇！
There's a snake in my boot!
听那个！让我们来看看它
Listen to that! Let's see it.
我打赌它是同一类型
I bet it's the same type.
不 谢谢 我的缝在里面
No, thanks, mine's sewn inside.
博在这附近吗？因为我们需要...
Is Bo around here? Because we need...
哦
Oh.
商店即将开业
The store is about to open.
别担心 我们会把你带到没人会看到我们的地方
Don't worry, we'll take you where no one will see us.
不好了 我们不能留下来
Oh, no. We can't stay.
是的你可以
Yes, you can.
我们走了
We got to go.
你不能离开 你有我需要的东西
You can't leave yet. You have what I need.
就在里面
Right inside there.
第二天回到那盏灯
Returned that lamp the next day.
你在开玩笑吧！
You're kidding me!
妈妈 我们现在可以去公园吗？
Mom, can we go to the park now?
和谐！
Harmony!
请停止他
Stop him, please.
这是怎么回事？
What's going on?
来吧！我们走吧！
Come on! Let's go!
他来了 他来了！我看到了他！
He's coming, he's coming! I see him!
叉子我们得离开......温迪！
Forky We got to get out of... Woody!
我想加入你的团队 男孩们
I'd like to join your posse, boys.
但首先 我要唱一首小歌
But first, I'm gonna sing a little song.
奶奶 看看我发现了什么
Grandma, look what I found.
我可以带它去公园吗？
Can I take it to the park Sure.
妈妈 她从商店里有足够的玩具
Mom, she has enough toys from the store.
哦 没关系 无论如何 没有人买这些玩具
Oh, it's fine. Nobody buys the toys anyway.
谢谢 奶奶！
Thanks, Grandma!
绮山楂！
Yee-haw!
妈妈 我们可以参加狂欢节吗？
Mom, can we go to the carnival?
我们要去公园
We're going to the park.
也许以后 亲爱的
Maybe later, sweetie.
温迪的任何迹象？
Any sign of Woody?
我没有看到他！嘘！
I don't see him! Shh!
也许我们应该放弃分叉
Maybe we should have gone with the fork.
汤匙更安全
The spoon is safer.
嗯
Mmm.
的叉子？
Forky?
什么是叉子？
Where's Forky?
妈妈！爸！
Mom! Dad!
- 怎么了 亲爱的？ - 你还好吗？
- What's wrong, honey? - Are you okay?
我找不到叉子了！他失踪了！
I can't find Forky! He's missing!
哦 邦妮 没关系
Oh, Bonnie, it'll be all right.
我确定他在某处
I'm sure he's here somewhere.
你知道 如果你没找到他
You know, if you don't find him,
你可以做一个新的
you can make a new one.
没有！只有一个派克！
No! There's only one Forky!
呃......我们去外面吧
Uh... Let's go look outside.
也许他在某个地方摔倒了
Maybe he fell on the ground somewhere.
哦 可怜的邦妮
Oh, poor Bonnie.
我们会找到他的 好吗？
We're gonna find him, okay?
我们必须找到他 妈妈 他需要我
We have to find him, Mom. He needs me.
温迪是对的
Woody was right.
我们都应该保护器具
We all should have been safeguarding the utensil.
为什么温迪还没回来？
Why isn't Woody back yet?
你觉得他输了吗？
Do you think he's lost?
嗡嗡声 我们该怎么办？我们做什么 巴斯？
Buzz, what do we do? What do we do, Buzz?
我们做什么 巴斯 巴斯！我 呃......
What do we do, Buzz Buzz! I, uh...
嗡嗡声 温迪会怎么做？
Buzz. What would Woody do?
呃 跳出一辆行驶的车辆
Eh, jump out of a moving vehicle.
温迪会怎么做？
What would Woody do?
这是一项秘密任务
It's a secret mission
在未知的空间 我们走吧！
in uncharted space. Let's go!
我想我得走了
I think I have to go.
你去哪里'为什么？
Where Where you goin' Why?
我们都应该去吗？
Should we all go?
- 我们去吗？ - 然后什么？
- Are we going? - And then what?
没时间解释！攻击！
No time to explain! Attack!
没时间解释！
No time to explain!
- 不好了！ - 嗡嗡声！
- Oh, no! - Buzz!
好吧 每个人都跳出窗外是什么？
Okay, what is with everyone jumping out the window?
温迪和叉子最后一次出现在高速公路上
Woody and Forky were last seen on the highway.
但是高速公路在哪里？
But where is the highway?
弹弓机动就是我们所拥有的！
The slingshot maneuver is all we've got!
全速前进！
Full speed ahead!
谢谢 内心的声音！
Thanks, inner voice!
喜雅！
Hi-ya!
高速公路
The highway.
在路上 温迪！
On my way, Woody!
拉德
Rad.
嘿!一步一步！
Hey! Step right up!
放下你的钱！
Put your money down!
让自己成为真正的巴斯光年！
Get yourself a real Buzz Lightyear!
嘿!嘿!
Hey! Hey!
和谐 亲爱的 防晒霜
Harmony, honey. Sunscreen.
好的
Okay.
牛仔先生 马上回来吧
Be right back, Mr. Cowboy.
好的 古董店 古董店......
Okay. Antique store, antique store...
Oh, that way!
哦 那样！
你看到他们了吗？那里有多少？
Did you see 'em? How many are there?
哇 哇 我们有一大堆露营者！
Whoa, whoa. We got a busload of campers!
他们来了！
Here they come!
- 嗯？ - 游戏时间 宝贝！
- Huh? - Playtime, baby!
哦 宝贝！这是玩的好日子 对吧？
Oh, baby! It's a good day to play, huh?
我对吗？
Am I right?
咦？
Huh?
“你好 牛仔先生 你今天好吗？”
"Hello, Mr. Cowboy. How are you today?"
“你喜欢骑马吗？”
"Do you like riding horses?"
想玩秋千吗？
Wanna play on the swings?
等等我！
Wait for me!
博？
Bo?
来吧
Come on.
博！
Bo!
哦 我简直不敢相信你！
Oh, I can't believe it's you!
博皮！
Bo Peep!
我从未想过我会再次见到你！
I never thought I'd see you again!
- 那么 哪个孩子是你的？ - 哪一个是你的？
- So, which kid is yours? - Which one is yours?
没有 没有人
None. No one.
等等 你是一个丢失的玩具？你是一个丢失的玩具？
Wait, you're a lost toy? You're a lost toy?
那是糟糕的 那很棒
That's awful. That's great.
嗯 我的意思是 非常好......
Huh I mean, awfully great...
你在这里迷路了
that you are lost out here.
- 臭鼬 臭鼬 臭鼬！ - 小心！
- Skunk, skunk, skunk! - Watch out!
咦？
Huh?
我告诉过你不要这么快开车
I told you not to drive so fast.
You almost ran him over.
你几乎让他过来了
哦 嘿 伙计们！
Oh, hey, guys!
哇！抓住那里！
Whoa! Hold on there!
好的！我也想你
Okay! I missed you, too.
如果不是鲍比·古斯？
If it isn't Bobby Gus?
呃......左撇子？
Uh... Lefty?
比利 山羊和格鲁夫
Billy, Goat, and Gruff.
对！对！对！对不起大家
Right! Right! Right! Sorry, guys.
女孩 女孩！当然！
Girls. Girls! Of course!
好的 好的
All right, all right.
好的 我们来看看你 你需要修理吗？
Okay, let's get a look at you. You need any repairs?
修理不 我很好
Repairs No, I'm fine.
嘿!很好找 女孩们
Hey! Nice find, girls.
你从哪里得到这些东西？
Where did you get all this stuff?
这里和那里
Here and there.
你知道 有些孩子比其他孩子玩得更粗糙......
You know, some kids play rougher than others...
所以我尽力做好准备
so I try to be prepared.
你自己出去多久了？
How long have you been out on your own?
七个美妙的岁月！
Seven fantastic years!
七？
Seven?
你不会相信我见过的东西
You would not believe the things I've seen.
呃 不
Uh, no.
- 演出  - 哟！
- Gigs. - Yo!
来吧有人要我见你
Come on out. There's someone I want you to meet.
马上
Be right down.
情况如何？我们走出城镇或......
What's the situation? We heading out of town or...
哇！这是谁？
Whoa! Who's this?
你还记得我告诉你的布娃娃吗？
You remember the rag doll I told you about?
牛仔啊！
The cowboy Yep!
没门！
No way!
- 不要盯着看  - 我完全盯着看
- Don't stare. - I'm totally staring.
温迪 这是吉格·曼迪宝斯
Woody, this is Giggle McDimples.
哦 嗨 咯咯
Oh, hi, Giggle.
哇 你没告诉我他是警察
Whoa, you didn't tell me he was a cop.
你好 警长
Howdy, Sheriff.
警官吉格·曼迪宝斯
Officer Giggle McDimples.
我为明尼·阿波利斯运行宠物巡逻
I run Pet Patrol for Mini-Opolis.
是的 搜索和救援
Yeah, search and rescue.
蚂蚁 毛毛虫
Ants, caterpillars,
- 迷你贵宾犬 蜘蛛  - 小屋！小屋！小屋！
- miniature poodles, spiders. - Hut! Hut! Hut!
卡尔！你去哪里了？
Carl! Where you headed?
战斗卡尔刚刚听说有生日派对......
Combat Carl just heard there's a birthday party...
在主街的操场上
at the playground on Main Street.
有传言说他们有两个皮纳塔
Rumor has it they got two pinatas.
那可能是20到30个孩子 太好了！
That could be 20 to 30 kids. Nice!
哦耶！与卡尔的刚开'一起玩！
Oh, yeah! Combat Carl's gettin' played with!
你们在吗？
You guys in?
你打赌！温迪 你会喜欢这个！
You bet! Woody, you are gonna love this!
呃 不 我不能 先生
Uh, no, I can't, sir.
博 我需要回到我的孩子身边
Bo, I need to get back to my kid.
你有一个孩子？
What You got a kid?
是啊
Yeah.
战胜对手的方法 士兵
Way to beat the odds, soldier.
皮 在操场上认识你
Meet you at the playground, Peep.
战斗卡尔有一个皮纳塔派对崩溃
Combat Carl's got a pinata party to crash.
好的 搬出去 小屋！小屋！小屋！
All right, move out. Hut! Hut! Hut!
那么 你 呃 和一个孩子在一起？
So, you're, uh, with a kid?
这不是安迪 是吗？
It's not Andy, is it?
不不不 他去上大学了
No, no, no. He went off to college.
但是他把我们交给了邦妮
But he gave us to Bonnie.
你有一个小女孩没办法！
You have a little girl No way!
是啊 这就是我出门的原因
Yeah, yeah. It's why I'm out here.
她的另一个玩具被困住了
Her other toy is trapped
在这家古董店 我必须......
in this antique store, and I have to...
第二次机会古董？
Second Chance Antiques?
我们知道商店
We know that store.
那很棒 太棒了！
That's great. That is great!
如果你了解商店 你真的可以
If you know the store, you could really
帮我找到他......没办法
help me find him... No way.
我们在那里浪费了多年
We wasted years there,
只是坐在架子上 收集灰尘
just sitting on the shelf, collecting dust.
哦 博 那太糟糕了
Oh, Bo, that's awful.
但我没有选择
But I don't have a choice.
我必须从加比那里拿到那个玩具
I have to get that toy from Gabby.
哇 避开那个古怪的东西
Whoa. Steer clear of that weirdo.
如果我是你 我会减少损失并回家
If I were you, I'd cut my losses and go home.
但邦妮需要他通过幼儿园
But Bonnie needs him to get through kindergarten.
孩子们每天都会失去玩具 邦妮会克服它
Kids lose toys every day. Bonnie will get over it.
不 不...
No, no...
你看 邦妮就像莫莉需要你一样需要他
You see, Bonnie needs him just like Molly needed you.
噢 没有 对不起 女孩们
Aw, no. Sorry, girls.
莫莉不在这里
Molly's not here.
莫莉博 我不知道你有一个孩子
Molly Bo, I didn't know you had a kid.
那是很久以前的事
That was a long time ago.
哦 博的孩子很特别
Oh, Bo's kid was something special.
她是最可爱的东西......
She was the cutest thing...
但是害怕黑暗
but so afraid of the dark.
这只是一个阶段
It was just a phase.
哦 你一开始不在那里
Oh, you weren't there in the beginning.
每天晚上听莫莉哭泣......
Hearing Molly cry each night...
它打破了每个玩具的心脏
it broke every toy's heart.
然后 博进了房间
And then, Bo came into the room.
她的灯是唯一让莫莉感到安全的灯
Her lamp was the only thing that made Molly feel safe.
妈妈会让她整夜保持博
Mom would let her keep Bo on all night.
哈！谁知道你这么软弱？
Ha! Who knew you were such a softy?
莫莉会睡着了
And Molly would fall asleep
她的手搁在博的脚上
with her hand resting on Bo's feet.
好的！好的 我知道了
Okay! Okay. I get it.
博 我的孩子真的需要这个玩具
Bo, my kid really needs this toy.
你会帮我吗？为了旧时的缘故
Will you help me? For old times' sake.
好的 好的
All right, all right.
谢谢！哦!
Thank you! Oh!
哦谢谢！好吧
Oh, thank you! All right.
猜猜我们是这样做的 让我们骑吧！
Guess we're doing this. Let's ride!
第二次机会古董 并踩到它
Second Chance Antiques, and step on it.
噢！
Ow!
嘿 嘿！
Hey, hey!
- 本森 我们完成了吗？ - 喔！
- Benson, are we finished? - Ow!
哦 感觉很好！
Oh, that feels great!
看那个！新的一样
Look at that! Good as new.
是啊 谢谢 呃 本森
Yeah. Thank you, uh, Benson.
呃 那么 嗯 什么时候温迪回来了？
Uh, so, um, when's Woody coming back?
就像我说的那样 很快
Like I said, soon.
他不会忘记你
He won't forget about you.
你怎么知道的？
How do you know?
你的孩子的名字写在你的脚上
You have your child's name written on your feet.
棒
Sticks.
这使你成为一个非常重要的玩具
That makes you a very important toy.
这正是温迪所说的
That's exactly what Woody says.
嗯 有趣
Hmm. Interesting.
阿婆好！我们回来了！
Hi, Grandma! We're back!
她回来了
She's back.
她是谁？
Who is she?
和谐
Harmony.
等一下......她带了温迪
Wait a second... she took Woody.
她失去了他吗？
Did she lose him?
不 我的和谐是完美的
No. My Harmony is perfect.
叉子 这是下午茶时间 这是下午茶时间
Forky, it's tea time. It's tea time.
喔 呼！什么是下午茶时间？
Whoo-hoo! What is tea time?
哦 我会告诉你的
Oh, I'll show you.
一点点牛奶 两块糖
A little bit of milk, two lumps of sugar.
我一直在练习 我看起来怎么样？
I've been practicing. How do I look?
呃......高一点
Uh... A little higher.
伸出你的小指
Stick out your pinky.
太好了！
Nice!
嗯！美味的！
Mmm! Delicious!
和谐 亲爱的 我要走了
Harmony, sweetie, I'm leaving.
快来给我一个拥抱
Come give me a hug.
妈妈 再见 我爱你
Bye, Mom. I love you.
当我的语音盒被修复时......
When my voice box is fixed...
我终于有机会了
I'll finally get my chance.
现在 关于我们的朋友温迪
Now, about our friend Woody.
我想知道关于他的一切
I wanna know everything about him.
哦 是的 温迪
Oh, yeah, Woody.
我一生就认识那个人 两天！
I've known that guy my whole life. Two days!
嘿 你知道邦妮不是他的第一个孩子吗？
Hey, did you know that Bonnie was not his first kid?
他有另一个孩子 安迪
He had this other kid, Andy.
你知道吗？
And you know what?
嘘 嘿 光年
Psst. Hey, Lightyear.
嘿 在这里 天文学家
Hey, up here, Astro-boy.
如果你认为你可以出现
If you think you can just show up
并获得我们的最高奖项...
and take our top prize spot...
你错了！死了错了！
you're wrong! Dead wrong!
你不明白 我试图...
You don't understand. I'm trying to...
欺骗系统 和孩子一起去 是的 我们知道
Cheat the system and get with a kid Yeah, we know.
不 我需要......
No, I need...
一个孩子用无条件的爱淋浴你？
A child to shower you with unconditional love?
加入俱乐部 朋友
Join the club, pal.
是的 加入俱乐部！
Yeah, join the club!
来吧 帮我离开这里
Come on, help me get outta here.
我会帮你 用我的脚！
I'll help you. With my foot!
抓住他
Get him.
兔子 你在做什么嗯？
Bunny, what are you doing Hmm?
我无法联系到他 帮帮我 来吧
I can't reach him. Help me out here, come on.
哦 对不起 杜基 你知道 我不是读者
Oh, sorry, Ducky. I'm not a mind reader, you know.
有什么不明白的 嗯？
What's not to understand, hmm?
你会让我说出来吗？
You gonna make me say it?
什么？
What?
有了这些小腿
With these tiny legs,
没有你的帮助 我无法联系到你
I cannot reach without your help.
嗯 好的 这就是
Uh-huh. Okay This is what
我一直在谈论 兔子
I've been talking about, Bunny.
你需要注意力
You need to work on paying attention
和你的听力技巧
and your listening skills.
哈！
Ha!
你怎么样 骗子哈？
How you like that, cheater Huh?
是啊！
Yeah!
哦 到无限和我的脚！繁荣！
Oh, to infinity and my foot! Boom!
在遥远的星系中 你被踢了一脚！
In a galaxy far, far away, you got kicked in the head!
我怎么离开这里？
How do I get out of here?
这个星球是有毒的
This planet is toxic.
关闭头盔以节省氧气
Closing helmet to conserve oxygen.
在空间的真空中 他们听不到你的尖叫声！
In the vacuum of space, they cannot hear you scream!
噢！
Ow!
让我走！
Let go of me!
你离我远点！
Get off of me!
哦！所以 那就是重力感觉
Ooh! So, that's what gravity feel like.
是的 就是这样
Yeah, that's it.
嘿 你要去哪儿？
Hey, where you going?
太空人 你最好过来！
You better get over here, spaceman!
是的 让我们回到那里！
Yeah, put us back up there!
兔子 你在干嘛？他走了 走吧！
Bunny, what are you doing? He's getting away, let's go!
我正在努力！来吧！
I'm trying! Come on!
古董店 我们来了！
Antique store, here we come!
博 你为什么要在臭鼬中骑行？
Bo, why do you ride around in a skunk?
哇！臭鼬！
Whoa! Skunk!
一个臭鼬！
A skunk!
哦 我明白了 聪明
Oh, I get it. Smart.
玉米狗 玉米狗 玉米狗！
Corndogs, corndogs, corndogs!
为什么你开车这么差？
Why are you so bad at driving?
你有六只眼睛
You got six eyes.
谢谢你的降落
Thanks for the landing.
呃......来吧 跟我来
Uh... Come on, follow me.
- 我很好  - 他的脸！
- I'm fine. - His face!
那真好笑 我很好 别担心
That's hilarious. I'm fine. Don't worry.
一直发生
Happens all the time.
胶带！
Tape!
不错的藏身之处
Not a bad hiding spot.
是啊 留下臭鼬
Yeah. Leave the skunk.
- 我们稍后会解决它  -  10-4
- We'll fix it later. - 10-4.
这会更有趣
This will be more fun.
我们带你去那家商店吧！
Let's get you to that store!
好吧 溢出来 牛仔 这是什么交易？
Okay, spill it. The cowboy, what's the deal?
没有交易 嗯
There's no deal. Uh-huh.
不要对自己这样做 牛仔有个孩子
Don't do this to yourself. Cowboy's got a kid.
咯咯......相信我 我去过那儿
Giggle... Trust me. I've been there.
你了解我和他人 我并不自豪
You know about me and He-Man. I'm not proud.
嘘！他来了！
Shh! Here he comes!
哦 伙计......什么？
Oh, man... What?
不 不是你
No, not you.
第二次机会古董 直线前进
Second Chance Antiques, straight ahead.
入口处的人流量很大
Heavy foot traffic at the entrance.
最简单的方法是 - 屋顶 屋顶！
Easiest way in is - the roof. The roof!
我们去古董吧
Let's go antiquing.
坚持 稍等！
Hold on!
咦？
Huh?
哇！
Whoa!
你是怎么来到这里的？
How did you end up here?
我以为你被送给了一个新的家庭
I thought you were given to a new family.
哦 你知道它是怎么回事
Oh, you know how it goes.
Their little girl grew up
他们的小女孩长大了
并且不再需要我了 所以......
and didn't need me anymore, so...
哦 对不起 博
Oh, I'm sorry, Bo.
呃 谁需要一个孩子的房间......
Eh, who needs a kid's room...
什么时候可以拥有这一切？
when you can have all of this?
什么看着 警长？
Whatcha looking at, Sheriff?
什么哦 呃......
What Oh, uh...
那不是......不 呃 没什么
That wasn't... No, uh, nothing.
我在看商店 在那里
I was looking at the store. Right there.
我在看古董店
I was looking at the antique store.
- 傻笑 算下我们  - 五
- Giggle, count us down. - Five.
四点倒计时
Countdown for what Four.
你想去商店 不是吗？
You want to get to the store, don't you?
三 二 一！
Three. Two. One!
高速公路出口必须在某个地方
The highway exit has to be somewhere.
它在哪里？
Where is it?
流星雨！当心！
Meteor shower! Look out!
温迪？
Woody?
好工作 内心的声音
Good work, inner voice.
那么 你呢？你的新孩子怎么样？
So, how about you? How's your new kid?
邦妮哦 她很棒
Bonnie Oh, she's great.
杰西很喜欢它
Jessie is loving it.
杰西还和你在一起？
Jessie's still with you?
哦 是的 整个团伙还在一起
Oh, yeah, the whole gang's still together.
嗯 我的意思是 我们大多数人
Well, I mean, most of us.
雷克斯怎么样？
What about Rex?
是的 是的 雷克斯 波塞 斯林基......
Yeah, yeah, Rex, Bullseye, Slinky...
马铃薯头......嗡嗡声？
the Potato Heads... Buzz?
是的 巴斯也是
Yeah, Buzz, too.
当他听到我发现时 我迫不及待地想看到他的脸......
I cannot wait to see his face when he hears that I found...
博皮 巴斯！
Bo Peep Buzz!
我的老朋友！巴兹？
My old moving buddy! Buzz?
很高兴见到你！
It's so good to see you!
温迪 这是博皮！
Woody, it's Bo Peep!
你在这里做什么？你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here? What are you doing here?
巴斯 ...... 巴斯 ...... 巴斯 ......
Buzz... Buzz... Buzz...
巴斯光年来救援！
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
三年！三年！
Three years! Three years!
那是我们多久了
That's how long we've been
挂在那里等待一个孩子！
hanging up there waiting for a kid!
看 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry about that.
你毁了我们的生活 你太无耻了！
You ruined our lives. Shame on you!
这些家伙是谁？
Who are these guys?
光年答应我们一个孩子 你做了什么？
Lightyear promised us a kid. You did what?
我没有
I did not.
- 嘿！等一下！ - 吃我的毛绒！
- Hey! Wait a minute! - Eat my plush!
现在好了 来吧 停下来吧！
All right now, come on, stop it!
现在就把它剪掉！
Cut it out now!
来吧 伙计们 分手吧
Come on, guys, break it up.
伙计们 我有个孩子！
Guys, I have a kid!
你有一个孩子？
You got a kid?
像小孩子一样？
Like a kid-kid?
像一个人类的孩子 而不是小山羊？
Like a human kid, not a baby goat?
是啊 现在放开巴斯 跟我来吧
Yeah. Now let go of Buzz and come with me.
我带你去邦妮
I'll take you to Bonnie.
我们开始'小孩'是的！
We're gettin' a kid Yes!
我们小时候开始？
We're gettin' a kid?
我们要小孩子
We're gonna get a kid Kid
我们正在生孩子好吧 我们走吧
We're getting a kid All right, let's go.
我们会得到一些东西哦 我们会呃 呃 呃
We gonna get something, oh We gonna uh, uh, uh.
在哪里是叉子悠长的故事
Where's Forky Long story.
孩子 我们得到一个孩子孩子 孩子 孩子
Kid, we get a kid Kid, kid, kid.
我们要小孩子？我们要小孩 孩子/我>
We gonna kid? We gonna kid, kid /i>
他不在任何地方
He's not anywhere.
叉子走了
Forky's gone.
哦 亲爱的 对不起
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
好的 让我们再一次向外看
Okay. Let's look outside one more time.
但是我们必须继续开车 好吗？
But then we have to keep driving, okay?
他们即将离开！
They're about to leave!
- 离开？ - 他们做不到！
- Leaving? - They can't do that!
恐慌袭击了我！
The panic is attacking me!
嘿!看着它 伙计！我们做什么？
Hey! Watch it, buddy! What do we do?
我们必须阻止他们！怎么样？
We have to stop them! How?
我们可以让爸爸犯罪 所以他去监狱
We could frame Dad for a crime so he goes to jail.
或者回到过去 并警告温迪关于未来
Or go back in time and warn Woody about the future.
太疯狂了 时间是一个扁平的圆圈
That's crazy. Time is a flat circle.
杰西！
Jessie!
对不起 邦妮
I'm sorry, Bonnie.
我们到处寻找
We looked everywhere.
但我们现在需要开始 好吗？
But we need to get going now, okay?
我们可以为叉子留言吗...
Can we please leave a note for Forky...
所以他知道我们要去哪里？
so he knows where we're going?
他必须去幼儿园
He has to go to kindergarten.
咦？
Huh?
你在开玩笑吗我不能......
Are you kidding me I can't...
一切都很完美......我刚买了它
Everything is going perfect... I just bought it.
好的！爸爸会用一些话
Okay! Daddy's going to use some words.
How about we go to the carnival?
我们去狂欢节怎么样？
或者也许去看看镇上的一些商店？
Or maybe check out some of those shops in town?
你做了什么？
What did you do?
我们不会去任何地方 如果你明白我的观点
We're not going anywhere. If you get my point.
- 太棒了！ - 那才是天才！
- Brilliant! - That was genius!
干得好 杰西！
Nice work, Jessie!
我确信巴斯和温迪现在正在回来的路上
I'm sure Buzz and Woody are on their way back right now.
哇！
Whoa!
叉子在那里？
Forky is in there?
是啊
Yeah.
现在 坚持下去 我有个问题
Now, hold on. I have a question.
邦妮会更爱谁？ 杜基或我说我
Who will Bonnie love more? Ducky or me Say me.
不 说杜基 鸭子 兔子 兔子
No, say Ducky. Ducky. Bunny. Bunny.
好的 伙计们 游戏时间结束了
Okay, guys. Playtime is over.
你必须跟随我的领导
You have to follow my lead.
我们在一起 我们保持安静 清楚吗？
We stay together, we stay quiet. Are we clear?
绝对 带路
Absolutely. Lead the way.
你在跟我开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding me Move over.
你走了过来 不要再逼我了
You move over. Quit pushing me.
停止 嘘！
Stop. Shh!
哦 我的制造商！那只羊有三个头！
Oh, my maker! That sheep has three heads!
不不不！
No, no, no!
所有六只眼睛只是看着我的灵魂
What All six eyes just looked into my soul.
会做恶梦
Gonna have nightmares.
这很可能是你的叉子被保留的地方
That's most likely where your Forky is being kept.
好吧 这不是那么糟糕
All right, this isn't so bad.
我们只是不能被傻瓜看到
We just can't be seen by the dummies.
不只是假人
Not just the dummies.
她的内阁周围是一条暴露的过道护城河
Her cabinet is surrounded by a moat of exposed aisle.
龙漫游的地方
Where Dragon roams.
我们可以处理一只猫 没有
We can handle a cat. No.
不是这个
Not this one.
那是我们在内心看的样子吗？
Is that how we look on the inside?
- 有这么多......  - 绒毛
- There's so much... - fluff.
那么 你怎么建议我们到那儿去？
So, how do you propose we get up there?
我们可以直接穿过
We could go straight across.
怎么那是一个跳跃
How That's quite a jump.
我们知道完美的玩具可以提供帮助
We know the perfect toy to help.
哦 邦妮 看看吧
Oh, Bonnie, check it out.
- 看看所有这些很酷的东西  - 邦妮？
- Look at all this cool stuff. - Bonnie?
我们现在得到了叉子！
We got to get Forky now!
温迪 不要......坚持计划  10-4
Woody, don't... Stick to the plan. 10-4.
跟着我 收到
Follow me. Roger that.
温迪只是坐在壁橱里？没有游戏时间？
Woody just sits in the closet? With no playtime?
是的 他告诉我自己 他没用
Yeah, he told me himself, he's useless.
那是糟糕的
That's awful.
这漂亮的头发......你在做什么？
Such pretty hair... What are you doing?
你需要坚持这个计划
You need to stick to the plan.
但这是邦妮 她是对的......
But it's Bonnie. She's right...
我们也可以参加狂欢节吗？
Can we go to the carnival, too?
那里
There.
来吧 保持安静
Come on. Stay quiet.
你最好希望假人没有......
You better hope the dummies didn't...
哇！
Whoa!
我的羊！
My sheep!
我说了什么？我带领 你跟着
What did I say? I lead. You follow.
博 我很抱歉 真
Bo, I'm so sorry. Really.
告诉我如何提供帮助
Just tell me how to help.
你真的想帮忙吗？
You really wanna help?
然后不要管我 我让我的羊回来了
Then stay out of my way. I'm getting my sheep back.
其他人怎么样？
What about the others?
吉格知道该怎么做
Giggle knows what to do.
- 干得好  - 这是我们的目标
- Here you go. - That's our objective.
我们必须得到那把钥匙
We have to get that key.
这是内阁的唯一途径
It's the only way inside the cabinet.
你不能认真
You can't be serious.
我们该怎么做呢？
How are we supposed to do that?
好的
Okay.
你知道吗 留给我们
You know what, leave that to us.
我们确切地知道该怎么做
We know exactly what to do.
嗯 嗯
Mmm-hmm.
噢
Aw.
你们俩来自哪里？
Where did you two come from?
按键！马上给他们吧！他们在哪？
The keys! Give 'em up now! Where are they?
给我们钥匙！给我们钥匙！
Give us the keys! Give us the keys!
好吧 我们不这样做
Well, we're not doing that.
是的 是的 我同意 太明显了
Yeah, yeah, I agree, too visible.
这是一个好点 更微妙的东西
It's a good point. Something more subtle.
哦 “赢家 赢家 鸡肉晚餐”怎么样？
Ooh, what about "Winner, winner, chicken dinner"?
是
Yes.
按键！马上给他们吧！他们在哪？
The keys! Give 'em up now! Where are they?
呃......你在开玩笑 真？
Uh... you're kidding. Really?
好吧好吧 你刚才...
Okay, okay. You just...
好吧 好...
All right. Well...
哦 旧的“毛绒拉什”怎么样？
Oh, what about the old "Plush Rush"?
你去！
There you go!
哎呀 这是怎么回事？嘘！不要打断
Argh. Where is this going? Shh! Don't interrupt.
- 好的 对吧？ - 嗯？
- Okay, right? - Uh-huh?
不会发生 没有
Not gonna happen. N-O.
好的 你想要钥匙吗？
Okay, do you want the key or not?
你怎么了？
What is wrong with you?
What is wrong with...?
出什么问题了...？
我们只给了你三个很棒的想法
We just gave you three brilliant ideas.
说不 这是一回事
It's one thing to say no.
提供理由是另一个原因......
It's another to offer a reason...
我们如何获得该密钥？
How do we get that key?
你在开玩笑！
You're kidding!
真？
Really?
温迪回来了吗？
Woody's back?
你肯定是博皮和他在一起吗？
And you're sure it's Bo Peep who's with him?
谢谢本森
Thank you, Benson.
确保其他人准备就绪
Make sure the others are ready.
温迪回来了！
Woody's back!
我来了 邦妮！
I'm coming, Bonnie!
邦妮
Bonnie.
首先 我们必须为他的到来做好准备
First, we must prepare for his arrival.
准备？
Prepare?
你玩过捉迷藏吗？
Have you ever played hide-and-seek?
不 但听起来很复杂
No. But it sounds complicated.
哦 这很容易
Oh, it's easy.
我会教你的 好的好的
I'll teach you, okay Okay.
你要做的第一件事就是......
The first thing you do is...
我们中的一个找到了隐藏的地方......可怕
one of us finds a place to hide... Scary.
然后试图找到它们
Then tries to find them.
我们在做什么嘘！
What are we doing Shh!
只要站在那里安静！
Just stand there and be quiet!
我会说话
I'll do the talking.
嗨 蒂尼！
Hi, Tinny!
噢 很高兴见到你
Aw, nice to see you, too.
是的 他和我在一起
Yeah, he's with me.
我的朋友不 不 不
My friend No, no, no.
他是我的配件
He's my accessory.
- 大家好  - 博！
- Hey, guys. - Bo!
好久不见
Long time no see.
不能把它带出去 是吧？
Couldn't take it out there, huh?
嘿 道格 看到你更好的一半
Hey, Doug. Saw your better half
在商店的前面
at the front of the store.
是的 你弄乱了猫 你得到了爪子
Yeah, you mess with the cat, you get the claws.
博回来了！
Bo came back!
魔术8球是对的！
Magic 8-Ball was right!
劳驾 抱歉 你在这里做什么？
Excuse me. Sorry. What are you doing here?
我以为商店没有退货政策！
I thought the store had no return policy!
博 帮帮我吧
Bo, help me out.
我需要一个电池
I need a battery.
我们得到了这辆货车列车'！
We got to get this wagon train a-movin'!
- 同意  - 帮助 帮助 帮助
- Agreed. - Help, help, help.
骗子
Cheater.
你见过杜克吗？
Have you seen Duke?
他在后面
He's in the back.
看谁跳了40辆校车
Look who jumped 40 school buses
并重新回到我的生活中
and landed back into my life.
嗨 公爵！谁是牛仔？
Hi, Duke! Who's the cowboy?
杜克 遇见温迪 温迪 见面......
Duke, meet Woody. Woody, meet...
公爵卡布 加拿大最伟大的替身演员
Duke Caboom. Canada's greatest stuntman.
哦耶！
Oh, yeah!
- 是的！ - 嗯？
- Yes! - Huh?
他在冒充
He's posing.
公爵？
Duke?
杜克 我们需要......坚持下去 多一个
Duke, we need to... Hold on. One more.
哦耶！是什么让你回来 窥视？
Oh, yeah! What brings you back, Peep?
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
加比·加比有他的玩具和我的羊
Gabby Gabby has his toy and my sheep.
不 比利 山羊和格鲁夫？那些是我的女孩
No. Billy, Goat, and Gruff? Those are my girls.
你在做什么纠缠起来
What were you doing getting tangled up
和加比·加比？你比较清楚
with Gabby Gabby? You know better.
是的 有些玩具认为这是个好主意......
Yeah, some toy thought it would be a good idea...
徘徊在过道里
to wander into the aisle.
这没有任何意义
That doesn't make any sense.
它没有 是吗？
It doesn't, does it?
每个人都知道货架后面的最佳路线
Everybody knows the best route is behind the shelves.
这本来是一条更好的路线 不是吗？
That would have been a better route, wouldn't it?
哇 这个玩具听起来像个完全白痴
Wow, this toy sounds like a complete idiot.
他是这样的！
He does!
等等 你是那个玩具吗？
Wait, are you that toy?
所以 这是计划
So, here's the plan.
我们需要跳过过道到加比的内阁
We need to jump over the aisle to Gabby's cabinet.
而你就是这样做的玩具 没有
And you are the toy to do it. No.
公爵 不
Duke. Nope.
公爵公爵嗯嗯 没门！
Duke Duke Nuh-uh. No way!
公爵 公爵！通过 负
Duke. Duke! Pass. Negative.
公爵 被拒绝
Duke. Rejected.
哦 拜托 卡布先生 这非常重要
Oh, please, Mr. Caboom, this is really important.
我的孩子......
My kid...
你有一个孩子？
You have a kid?
呃...
Uh...
嘿 杜克 给我们看一些姿势 你怎么说？
Hey, Duke, show us some more poses, what do you say?
我有一个孩子 不好了
I had a kid. Oh, no.
瑞简
Rejean.
瑞简在圣诞节后送我的时候非常兴奋
Rejean was so excited when he got me after Christmas.
这是我生命中最快乐的节礼日
It was the happiest Boxing Day of my life.
那是公爵卡布
That's Duke Caboom,
骑着惊人的卡布特技周期！
riding the amazing Caboom stunt cycle!
卡布！
Caboom!
我已经准备好最终完成我的目标
I was ready to finally do what I was made to do.
卡布！
Caboom!
但当瑞简意识到我无法跳跃时
But when Rejean realized I couldn't jump
至于商业中的玩具......
as far as the toy in the commercial...
这是商业广告！这不是真的！
It's a commercial! It's not real!
瑞简把我扔了！
Rejean threw me away!
这不公平！
It's not fair!
为什么 瑞简为什么？
Why, Rejean Why?
好吧好吧 冷静 杜克
Okay, okay. Calm down, Duke.
That was a long time ago.
那是很久以前的事
现在 我们需要唯一的玩具
Right now, we need the only toy
谁能让我们撞到加比的内阁
who can crash us onto Gabby's cabinet.
崩溃？
Crash?
任何公爵卡布玩具都可以降落......
Any Duke Caboom toy can land...
但是你是唯一可以像你那样崩溃的人
but you are the only one that can crash the way you do.
我是啊！
I am Yes!
忘记瑞简 忘了你的广告
Forget Rejean. Forget your commercial.
成为公爵你现在是......
Be the Duke you are right now...
跳跃和崩溃的人！
the one who jumps and crashes!
是我现在的人
Be who I am right now.
幸运的是谁是卡努克？
Who's the Canuck with all the luck?
卡布？
Caboom?
谁是大白北的最伟大的？
Who's the greatest of the Great White North?
卡布！
Caboom!
谁是最壮观的冒失鬼
Who's the most spectacular daredevil
加拿大曾见过？
Canada has ever seen?
公爵卡布！
Duke Caboom!
你能跳一下吗？
Can you do the jump?
是的 我加拿大！
Yes, I Canada!
嗯
Uh-huh.
- 我们骑了  - 是的！
- We've got our ride. - Yes!
绮山楂！
Yee-haw!
哟 博！
Yo, Bo!
演出！你做到了！
Gigs! You made it!
干得好！
Good work!
How'd you get it?
你怎么样的？
我们如何获得该密钥？
How do we get that key?
那个挺难 非常困难
It was hard. Very difficult.
勉强活着 是啊
Barely made it out alive. Yeah.
So, you're welcome.
所以 欢迎你
好的 我们开工吧
Okay. Let's do this.
让我为你报道
Let me wrap that up for you.
在回家的路上不要发生任何事情
Don't want anything to happen to it on the way home.
好 那次销售给我们带来了一些时间
Good. That sale buys us some time.
等等
Wait for it.
好的 我们走吧！
All right, let's go!
那么 你在这里多久了？
So, how long were you in here?
我不知道 几年
I don't know. Couple years.
我不想坐在架子上等待我的生命发生
I didn't wanna sit on a shelf waiting for my life to happen.
所以 我离开了
So, I left.
哇
Wow.
你已经比我更好地处理了这个失去的玩具生活
You've handled this lost toy life better than I could.
噢 警长
Aw, Sheriff.
你卖得很短
You're selling yourself short.
我想你会成为一个失败的玩具
I think you'd make a great lost toy.
你真的不这么认为
You really don't think
你会再次进入一个孩子的房间 对吧？
you'll ever be in a kid's room again, huh?
不
Nope.
现在狂欢节穿越
And now with the carnival traveling through,
这是我们跳车的机会......
it's our chance to hop a ride...
离开小镇 你要走了？
and leave town. You're leaving?
当然可以
Sure am.
你有没有想过去那里看世界？
You ever think about getting out there, seeing the world?
没有孩子？
Without a kid?
不 你不能教这个旧玩具新技巧
No. You can't teach this old toy new tricks.
你会感到惊讶
You'd be surprised.
那么 你最初是如何在这家商店结束的？
So, how'd you end up in this store in the first place?
好吧 我在窗口看到了你的灯......
Well, I saw your lamp in the window...
我想也许你在里面......
and I thought maybe you were inside...
所以我 呃......
and so I, uh...
哇
Wow.
是啊
Yeah.
你会看那个吗？
Will you look at that?
这是我喜欢的商店的唯一部分
This is the only part of the store I ever liked.
对你和杜克来说 这将是一个很大的跳跃
That's gonna be quite a jump for you and Duke.
为了我？
For me?
我不是告诉你的吗？你跟他一起去
Didn't I tell you? You're going with him.
我是？
I am?
我们的房间
Let's caboom.
没关系 公爵是最棒的
It'll be fine, Duke's the best.
是的 在崩溃
Yeah, at crashing.
现在！
And now!
走！
Go!
哇！
Whoa!
哼 瑞简
Huh Rejean.
这是商业广告 这不是真的！
It's a commercial. It's not real!
我不能这样做！对不起 瑞简！
I can't do this! I'm sorry, Rejean!
不不不！
No, no, no!
什么是新的 猫咪？
What's new, pussycat?
叉子女孩？
Forky Girls?
叉子 你在哪里？
Forky, where are you?
你永远不会找到我
You're never gonna find me.
的叉子？
Forky?
温迪！你怎么找到我的？
Woody! How'd you find me?
博 我找到了他！你好
Bo, I found him! Hi.
等等 这是一个真正的分叉？
Wait, it's an actual fork?
博！博！博！
Bo! Bo! Bo!
巴斯！假人走了！
Buzz! The dummies are gone!
他们去哪儿了？
What Where'd they go?
好的 我们现在可以走了！
Okay, we can go now!
- 不 我需要找到我的女孩  - 你好 温迪
- No. I need to find my girls. - Hello, Woody.
嗨 博
Hi, Bo.
我的羊在哪里呀！
Where are my sheep Yeah!
看！温迪发现了我！
Look! Woody found me!
带上兔子！我太可爱了！
Take the bunny! I'm too cute to die!
- 你好！ - 哦 不 不！
- Hi-ya! - Oh, no, no!
温迪！
Woody!
我只是想说话 是的 我的语音盒！
I just wanna talk. Yeah, with my voice box!
拉！
Pull!
哇！
Whoa!
你是我最喜欢的副手
You're my favorite deputy.
有人毒死了水洞
Somebody's poisoned the water hole.
我想加入你的团队
I'd like to join your posse.
伸手去拿天空！
Reach for the sky!
女孩！
Girls!
算了吧
Drop it.
没有！没有！的叉子！
No! No! Forky!
我们得走了！等待！
We've got to go! Wait!
的叉子！
Forky!
温迪！
Woody!
邦妮的背包？
Bonnie's backpack?
啊！
Ahh!
傻笑！
Giggle!
不要让温迪离开！
Don't let Woody leave!
抓住！
Grab on!
杜克 让我们离开这里！
Duke, get us out of here!
好 ！
Oui!
在这里 小猫 小猫！
Here, kitty, kitty!
等待！我们没有叉子！
Wait! We don't have Forky!
温迪！
Woody!
的叉子！
Forky!
大家好吗？
Is everyone okay?
嘘 没关系
Shh. It's okay.
兔子兔子？
Bunny Bunny?
兔子！不不不不
Bunny! No, no, no, no.
不不不不
No, no, no, no.
哦 兔子！它会没事的
Oh, Bunny! It's gonna be okay.
叉子还在那里
Forky's still in there.
如果我们快点 我们可以在他们锁定他之前找到他
If we hurry, we can get him before they lock him up.
你想让我们回到那里吗？
You want us to go back in there?
我们几乎没有活着
We barely got out alive.
温迪 如果我们等待 那就更好了
Woody, it's better if we wait.
不不不 没时间了 我们可以很容易地回到里面
No, no, no. There's no time. We can easily get back inside.
但我看到了邦妮的......
But I saw Bonnie's...
根据我的统计 只有四个假人
By my count, there were only four dummies.
但背包......
But the backpack...
我们超过他们 所以我们有优势
We outnumber them. So we have the advantage.
温迪 看看我们！
Woody, look at us!
没有人和你在一起 结束了 好吗？
Nobody is with you. It's over, okay?
不不不不 我们在浪费时间 我们做得到
No. No, no, no. We are wasting time. We can do this.
- 来吧 拉弦  - 这不值得
- Come on, Pull-string. - It's not worth it.
是的 是的 听她说！
Yeah, yes, listen to her!
没有人想要这个！我做！
Nobody wants this! I do!
为什么 因为！
Why Because!
为什么只是因为！
Why Just because!
为什么？
Why?
因为这就是我要做的一切！
Because it's all I have left to do!
我什么都没有
I don't have anything else.
那么 我们其他人不算数？
So, the rest of us don't count?
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
邦妮需要分叉
Bonnie needs Forky.
不 你需要邦妮！
No. You need Bonnie!
睁开你的眼睛 温迪
Open your eyes, Woody.
那里有很多孩子
There's plenty of kids out there.
它不仅仅是你仍然坚持的那个
It can't be just about the one you're still clinging to.
它被称为忠诚度
It's called loyalty.
丢失的玩具不会理解的东西
Something a lost toy wouldn't understand.
我不是那个迷路的人
I'm not the one who's lost.
我们离开这里吧
Let's get out of here.
我们有一个早上离开的狂欢节
We've got a carnival that leaves in the morning.
来吧
Come on.
嗯 嗯
Mmm-hmm.
我们会找到自己的孩子
We'll find our own kid.
你疯了
You're crazy.
博！
Bo!
再见 温迪 祝你好运
Bye, Woody. Good luck with Bonnie.
温迪 你尽力而为
Woody, you did all you could.
该回家了
Time to go home.
没有
No.
温迪
Woody.
我不会把玩具留在后面 巴斯
I don't leave toys behind, Buzz.
是的 但是 温迪 你真的要离开......
Yeah, but, Woody, you're actually leaving...
现在不要 永远不会
Not now. Not ever.
他把我留在了身后
And he left me behind.
现在 内心的声音是什么？
What now, inner voice?
任务完成 回到基地
Mission accomplished. Return to base.
回到房车？温迪怎么样？
Go back to the RV? What about Woody?
我们要回家了 太空游侠
We're going home, space ranger.
回落 这个星球......
Fall back, this planet...
撤退！还有......
Retreat! There's too...
走！飞的时候！退出...返回...运行...
Go! Time to fly! Exit the... Back... Run...
出去！回到星际司令部
Get out! Returning to Star Command.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
非常感谢 内心的声音
Thanks a lot, inner voice.
和谐 亲爱的 帮奶奶关门过夜
Harmony, honey, help Grandma close up for the night.
好的 那我们可以去狂欢节吗？
Okay. Then can we go to the carnival?
当然
Sure.
- 啊！ - 你好 温迪
- Ahhh! - Hello, Woody.
我知道你会回来的
I knew you'd be back.
你不认识我
You don't know me.
但是我愿意
But I do.
你被留在壁橱里 感觉无用......
You were left in the closet, feeling useless...
想知道你是否会被玩弄
wondering if you'll ever get played with.
没有叉子 我不会离开
I'm not leaving without Forky.
我们能就一件事达成一致吗？
Can we agree on just one thing?
什么？
What?
那是为了一个孩子
That being there for a child
是玩具可以做的最高贵的事情
is the most noble thing a toy can do.
好的
Okay.
开箱即用我有缺陷
I was defective right out of the box.
我只能想象它一定对你来说是什么样的
I can only imagine what it must have been like for you.
你和安迪一起度过的那段时间......
All that time you spent with Andy...
和他一起骑自行车第一次......
riding a bike with him for the first time...
当他剥了膝盖时安慰他......
comforting him when he skinned his knee...
自豪地看着他长大
proudly watching him grow up.
然后你有了邦妮的第二次机会......
And then you got a second chance with Bonnie...
她在学校害怕时给她安慰......
giving her comfort when she's scared at school...
在她最需要的时候帮助她
helping her when she needs it most.
你经历过所有的跌宕起伏
You've been there through all their ups and downs.
请
Please.
跟我说实话
Be honest with me.
这听起来很精彩吗？
Was it as wonderful as it sounds?
它是
It was.
我想要的只是其中一个时刻的机会
All I want is a chance for just one of those moments.
我会以你的方式给予任何被爱的东西
I'd give anything to be loved the way you have.
离开我叉子吧
Just leave me Forky.
邦妮需要他
Bonnie needs him.
当然
Of course.
瘪胎是固定的！
The flat tire is fixed!
来吧 温迪 快点
Come on, Woody, hurry up.
他在哪里？
Where is he?
- 嗡嗡声！ - 嗡嗡声！
- Buzz! - Buzz!
- 温迪在哪里？ - 还有迪奇？
- Where's Woody? - And Forky?
我们有一个情况
We have a situation.
他们需要从古董店提取
They need to be extracted from the antique store.
我们怎么做？
How do we do that?
好的 让我们确保我们拥有一切
Okay, let's make sure we have everything.
最后
Finally.
没关系 现在任何一分钟......
It's okay. Any minute now...
邦妮会注意到她的背包丢失了
Bonnie will notice her backpack is missing.
她会意识到她把它留在了古董店......
She'll realize she left it at the antique store...
我们会回到那里
and we'll head back in there.
好的 看起来我们拥有一切
Okay. Looks like we have everything.
你好 邦妮 对
You good, Bonnie Yup.
大 我们离开这里吧
Great. Let's get out of here.
超越无限！
嗯 哦 呃 你的背包在古董店里！我们走吧！
Great. Let's get out of here.
哦 不 我的背包！
我把背包留在了古董店里！
Great. Let's get out of here.
好的 天才 我们现在做什么？
Okay, genius, what do we do now?
嗯
Hmm.
扫描周长
Scanning perimeter.
全功率激光！
Laser at full power!
嗡嗡声 你在做什么？我在想
Buzz, what are you doing? I'm thinking.
亲爱的 请你把那个玩具关掉？
Honey, will you please shut that toy off?
是的 我明白了
Yeah, I got it.
攻击！流星雨！当心！
Attack! Meteor shower! Look out!
这是未知空间的秘密任务！我们走吧！
It's a secret mission in uncharted space! Let's go!
巴斯光年来救援！
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
邦妮 你怎么关掉这个？
Bonnie, how do you turn this off?
全速前进！
Full speed ahead!
- 打开吊舱门！ - 我不知道
- Open the pod bay doors! - I don't know.
现在只是你和我 学员
It's just you and me now, cadet.
遇险信号来自那枚火箭
A distress signal is coming from that rocket.
把它扔进抽屉里
Just toss it in the drawer.
To infinity and beyond!
把它扔进抽屉里
Uh-oh. Uh, your backpack's in the antique store! Let's go!
Oh, no, my backpack!
把它扔进抽屉里
I left my backpack in the antique store!
你呢？
You did?
好吧 让我们一起来吧
All right, let's swing by and get it.
啊!我无法相信那个牛仔的神经
Ugh! I can't believe the nerve of that cowboy.
Ugh! I can't believe
the nerve of that cowboy.
我的意思是 他认为他是谁？
I mean, who does he think he is?
究竟！
Exactly!
他的方式不合时宜
He was way out of line.
你做了正确的事让他落后
You did the right thing leaving him behind.
- 嘿 羊排？ - 嗯
- Hey, Lamb Chops? - Hmm.
海岸很清楚 哦
Coast is clear. Oh.
前往中间
Head to the middle.
当狂欢节明天离开时
When the carnival leaves tomorrow,
我们会藏在那里
we'll hide right there.
呃 没办法！那东西
Uh, no way! Stuff that.
真棒
Awesome.
坚持我 你会没事的
Stick with me. You'll be fine.
- 准备好了？ - 不！
- Ready? - No!
另一件事
And another thing,
温迪向你求助 各就各位...
Woody asked you for help. On your mark...
而且他那样对待你？
And he treats you like that?
定下来......他只关心自己
Get set... He only cares about himself.
没有！
No!
你错了
You're wrong.
温迪总是试图让他的孩子做对
Woody's always trying to do right by his kid.
让每个人都处于危险之中
By putting everyone in danger.
啊 那种疯狂的忠诚只是......
Ugh. That kind of crazy loyalty just...
你必须爱他
You got to love him for it.
哇 现在说什么？
Whoa, say what now?
嘿 嘿 嘿 博！计划是什么？
Hey, hey, hey, Bo! What's the plan?
把我填入这里
Fill me in here.
进来！我们要回去了
Get in! We're going back.
我们刚来到这里
We just got here.
你听说博！我们回去了！
You heard Bo! We're going back!
移动你的毛绒！让我们骑吧！
Move your plush! Let's ride!
你是我的最爱...
You're my favorite...
好极了！
Yay!
你是我最好的朋友
You are my best friend.
让我们玩一整天！
Let's play all day!
哦 本森！你听到了吗？
Oh, Benson! Did you hear that?
不是那么可爱吗？
Isn't that lovely?
喝茶的时间
Time for tea.
哦 谢谢你 温迪 谢谢！
Oh, thank you, Woody. Thank you!
我所有的梦想
All my dreams
因为你而成真
are coming true because of you.
谢谢！谢谢！
Thank you! Thank you!
呃 不客气
Uh, you're welcome.
是的 本森
It's time, Benson.
再见 叉子 我会想念我们的谈话
Goodbye, Forky. I'm going to miss our talks.
我也是 祝你好运 加比
Me, too. Good luck, Gabby.
Thank you, my little utensil.
谢谢你 我的小器具
再见 加比！再见 本森！
Bye, Gabby! Goodbye, Benson!
他太可怕了
He is terrifying.
你好 你好
Hello. Hi.
邦妮？
Bonnie?
我可以帮你什么吗？
Can I help you with anything?
是啊 我们打电话给背包
Yeah. We called about the backpack.
哦 是的 我找不到它
Oh, yes. I couldn't find it.
随意环顾四周
Feel free to look around.
快！在她找到它之前！
Quick! Before she finds it!
看！有和谐
Look! There's Harmony.
你让我很幸福！
You make me so happy!
让我们成为最好的朋友
Let's be best friends.
哦 就是这样！
Oh, this is it!
我们要回家了 叉子！
We're going home, Forky!
咦？
Huh?
的叉子！哦!
Forky! Oh!
不不不 温迪 看！它真的发生了！
No, no, no. Woody, look! It's really happening!
我是加比·加比 我爱你
I'm Gabby Gabby, and I love you.
我要哭了
I'm gonna cry.
哦 你有什么？
Oh, what have you got there?
我找到了这个老娃娃
I found this old doll.
如果你愿意 你可以把它带回家
You can take it home if you want.
罗
Nah.
发生了什么事加比应该是她的玩具
What happened Gabby was supposed to be her toy.
有我的背包！
There's my backpack!
妈妈 它在这里
Mom, it's over here.
的叉子！
Forky!
妈妈 我找到了他！
Mom, I found him!
哦 他就在那里！
Oh, there he is!
现在 请把他留在那里
Now, please leave him in there,
所以他不会再迷路了
so he doesn't get lost again.
但是加比怎么样？
But what about Gabby?
叉子 非常仔细地听我说
Forky, listen to me very carefully.
这个很重要
This is important.
告诉巴斯让RV进入旋转木马
Tell Buzz to get the RV to the merry-go-round.
你明白？
You understand?
绝对 什么是旋转木马？
Absolutely. What is a merry-go-round?
与马灯和马匹的斯帕尼骑
The spinny ride with lights and horses.
哦 你的意思是旋转木马 是!
Oh. You mean a carousel. Yes!
旋转木马 是!在旋转木马上见我
Carousel. Yes! Meet me at the carousel.
得到它了
Got it.
爱说话的！嘿 加比！
Gabby! Hey, Gabby!
你可以让你的语音盒回来
You can have your voice box back.
我不再需要它了
I don't need it anymore.
哦 是的 你这样做
Oh, yes, you do.
和谐不是你唯一的机会 加比
Harmony wasn't your only chance, Gabby,
但我们必须快点 来吧
but we have to hurry. Come on.
不 和谐是我的机会
No. Harmony was my chance.
我的时间结束了
My time's over.
现在 请走开
Now, please go away.
你听到了吗？
You hear that?
一位朋友曾告诉我......
A friend once told me...
“那里有很多孩子 ”
"There are plenty of kids out there."
其中一个名叫邦妮
And one of them is named Bonnie.
她现在正在等你
She's waiting for you, right now.
她还不知道
She just doesn't know it yet.
如果你错了怎么办？
What if you're wrong?
好吧 如果你坐在架子上 你的余生......
Well, if you sit on a shelf the rest of your life...
你永远都找不到 好吗？
you'll never find out, will you?
他是对的
He's right.
我从最好的方面学到了这一点
I learned that from the best.
来吧 加比
Come on, Gabby.
我们来找你邦妮吧
Let's get you to Bonnie.
旋转木马？
The carousel?
是的 这是骑马和灯光的马匹
Yeah, it's the spinny ride with lights and horses.
温迪说要在那里见他
Woody said to meet him there.
开玩笑吧！我们怎么做？
You got to be kidding! How do we do that?
哦!我们可以 呃......
Oh! We could, uh...
我们不是把爸爸送进监狱
We are not sending Dad to jail.
你没什么好玩的
You're no fun.
左转0.5英里
Left turn in 0.5 miles.
等一会儿 我有个主意
Wait a second. I have an idea.
臭鼬！
Skunk!
太多人 需要一条替代路线
Too many people. Gonna need an alternate route.
我们能及时把它带到旋转木马上吗？
Will we make it to the carousel in time?
是的 我们加拿大！
Yes, we Canada!
它是什么？
What What is it?
重新计算 右转
Recalculating. Take a right.
什么是对的？
What A right?
右转
Right turn ahead.
呵呵  GPS听起来很有趣吗？
Huh. Does the GPS sound funny to you?
亲爱的 没关系 开车吧
Honey, it's fine. Just drive.
嗯 我觉得这听起来很有趣
Hmm, I thought it sounded funny.
另一个权利！
Another right!
对 采取另一种权利
Right. Take another right.
嗯另一个真的吗？
Huh Another right Really?
右转！现在！
Turn right! Now!
右转！
Turn right!
- 我们正在回头  - 有旋转木马！
- We're headin' back. - There's the carousel!
你认为温迪会及时赶到那儿吗？
Do you think Woody
will get there in time?
不 算了吧 决不 没有 没办法 下降
Do you think Woody will get there in time?
Nope. Forget it. Never. No. No way. Declined.
没有骰子 被拒绝 杜克 杜克 你有这个
No dice. Rejected. Duke, Duke, you got this.
这是转盘的最快方式
This is the fastest way to the carousel.
你做了最后一跳
You made the last jump.
是的 但那是4英尺 这是40！
Yeah, but that was 4 feet. This is 40!
究竟！ 公爵卡布永远不会重演噱头
Exactly! Duke Caboom would never repeat a stunt.
不 他永远不会这样做 不不不
No. He'd never do that. No, no, no.
他是继续坠毁40英尺的玩具
He's the toy that went on to crash 40 feet
进入那个目标！
into that target!
是啊 他是
Yeah, he is.
我是公爵卡布！
I'm Duke Caboom!
天啊 我可以做这个！
Oh, man. I can do this!
是的 你加拿大！
Yes, you Canada!
闭着眼睛 我能做到
I can do it with my eyes closed.
是的 你......什么？
Yes, you... What?
- 三二一 走！什么不 等等！
- Three, two, one. Go! - What No, wait!
他在做什么哦 不
What is he doing Oh, no.
这是给你的 瑞简
This is for you, Rejean.
卡布
Caboom.
是!
Yes!
他做到了！
He did it!
好的 轮到我们了！
All right, our turn!
你听到了治安官 我们走吧
You heard the sheriff. Let's go.
绮山楂！
Yee-haw!
另一个权利！
Another right!
另一个吧？这是错误的方式
Another right? That's the wrong way.
你确定愚蠢出租吗？
Are you sure Stupid rental.
- 我转过身来  - 不！
- I'm turning us around. - No!
- 嗯？ - 重新计算
- Huh? - Recalculating.
右转
Turn right.
- 必须打破  - 不！没有！
- Must be broken. - No! No!
怎么了？
What is happening?
亲爱的你在做什么？慢一点！
Honey, what are you doing? Slow down!
我不能！我不能！
I can't! I can't!
- 按下制动器 按下！ - 我正在努力
- Press the brake. Press it! - I'm trying.
在RV上有一个视觉 向南行驶
Got a visual on the RV, heading southbound.
爱说话的？
Gabby?
我想她已经迷路了
I think she's lost.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
改变计划
Change of plans.
拉过来
Pull over.
我不能！这是出租！
I can't! This is a rental!
我不知道发生了什么！
I don't know what's happening!
我很紧张
I'm so nervous.
如果她不喜欢我怎么办？爱说话
What if she doesn't like me? Gabby.
我不知道我是否可以这样做
I don't know if I can do this.
加比 就像你说的那样
Gabby, it's just like you said.
这是玩具可以做的最高贵的事情
This is the most noble thing a toy can do.
好的
Okay.
只是让自己陷入光明之中
Just edge yourself a bit into the light.
不太远
Not too far.
而已
That's it.
完善
Perfect.
赢家 赢家......鸡肉晚餐
Winner, winner... Chicken dinner.
你也迷路了吗？
Are you lost, too?
我是加比·加比 你能和我做朋友不？
I'm Gabby Gabby. Will you be my friend?
我会帮你
I'll help you.
对不起 你能帮助我们吗？
Excuse me, can you... Can you help us?
哦 亲爱的 怎么了？
Oh, honey, what's wrong?
我找不到我的妈妈和爸爸
I can't find my mom and dad.
没关系 我会帮你找到它们
It's okay. I'll help you find them.
我相信他们并不远
I'm sure they're not far.
她就在我们旁边
She was right next to us.
她就在这儿！
She was right here!
我看了一会儿
And I looked away for one second.
妈妈！
Mommy!
我找不到你......
I couldn't find you...
然后我发现了这个娃娃
and then I found this doll.
你呢？
You did?
她的名字叫加比·加比
Her name is Gabby Gabby.
哇 我们确实这样做了
Whoa. We actually did that.
哦耶 是!
Oh, yeah. Yes!
那太精彩了
That was amazing.
伙计们 我们组建了一支伟大的球队
We make a great team, guys.
拉过来吧！
Pull over now!
快好了
Almost there.
停止！停止！
Stop! Stop!
我们在家吗？
Are we home?
咦？
Huh?
先生 请你走出车外吗？
Sir, will you please step out of the vehicle?
爸爸完全入狱了
Dad's totally going to jail.
每个人 上层 让我们继续前进
Everyone, topside. Let's move.
叉子 我为你做了一件非常重要的工作
Forky, I've got a very important job for you.
为了我？
For me?
祝你有一个美好的夜晚
Have a good night.
什么......？
What the...?
你在开玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me.
嘿
Hey.
嗯......这么久 牛仔
Um... So long, cowboy.
快乐的小道
Happy trails.
比利 山羊 格拉夫 照顾她 女孩
Billy, Goat, Gruff. Take care of her, girls.
我很高兴再次见到你
I'm glad I got to see you again.
我......我不...
I... I don't...
再见 博
Goodbye, Bo.
嗡嗡声 我......我......
Buzz, I... I...
她会没事的
She'll be okay.
邦妮会没事的
Bonnie will be okay.
你确定？
You sure?
嘿 倾听你内心的声音
Hey. Listen to your inner voice.
博？
Bo?
真的是她吗？
Is it really her?
我会被吓到 这是博！
I'll be danged, it's Bo!
杰西
Jessie.
博！
Bo!
哦!
Oh!
好久 叉子
So long, Forky.
叉子谁在看门？
Forky Who's watching the doors?
- 冲啊！ - 好家伙
- Go, go, go! - Oh, boy.
哦 我的天啊 遮阳篷 到底是怎么回事？
Oh, my goodness. The awning. What is going on?
这是否意味着温迪是一个丢失的玩具？
Does this mean Woody's a lost toy?
他没有迷路
He's not lost.
不再
Not anymore.
超越无限
To infinity... And beyond.
好极了！
Yay!
还有一个
There goes another one.
我们永远不会离开这里
We're never getting outta here.
嘘 青蛙腿
Psst. Frog legs.
在这里 彩虹连接
Up here, Rainbow Connection.
你和头斯先生想和一个孩子一起骑车吗？
You Mr. Toads wanna take a wild ride with a kid?
我们可以做到这一点
We can make that happen.
你真的可以吗？
You can Really?
哦耶！留给我们 耶利米
Oh, yeah! Leave it to us, Jeremiah.
噢
Aw.
好吧 干得好 伙计！
All right. Nice job, gang!
每个奖品都有一个孩子
Every prize with a kid.
接下来给我们留下什么
What's next Leave that to us.
我们确切地知道该怎么做 嗯 嗯
We know exactly what to do. Mmm-hmm.
毛绒拉什！
Plush Rush!
你喜欢这个 对吧？
How you like that, huh?
儿子 你匆匆忙忙！
You got plush-rushed, son!
舞蹈！
Dance!
舞蹈！那些膝盖！
Dance! Get those knees up!
让我们看看那些脚移动！喔！
Let's see those feet move! Whoo!
或者我们可以为孩子们提供更多玩具
Or we can get more toys to kids.
是的 我们这样做
Yeah, let's do that.
你真的有激光眼睛吗？
Do you really have laser eyes?
是啊
Yeah.
哇
Whoa.
嗨 玩具 再见 玩具
Hi, toys. Bye, toys.
杰西回来了！
Jessie's back!
什么一年级喜欢？告诉我一切！
What's first grade like? Tell me everything!
嗯 这是......
Well, it was...
“现在和解释”怎么样？
How was "Present and Explain"?
呃 你的意思是“显示并告诉”那里 大家伙
Uh, you mean "Show and Tell" there, big guy.
你看到有孩子吃糊吗？
You see any kids eat paste?
伙计们 听！
Guys, listen!
邦妮在一年级的时候度过了美好的一天
Bonnie had a great day in first grade.
她甚至在课堂上结识了新朋友
She even made a new friend in class.
哦 她已经结交了朋友
Oh, she's already making friends.
不 不 她结交了新朋友
No, no, she made a new friend.
来吧 没关系
Come on out, it's okay.
你好 我 呃......我是叉子
Hi. I'm, uh... I'm Forky.
垃圾？
Trash?
不 不 玩具 我是...我们都是玩具
No, no. Toy. I am a... We are all toys.
独特 漂亮的玩具
Unique, beautiful toys.
我会解释一切
I will explain everything.
我怎么活着？
How am I alive?
我不知道
I don't know.
翻译：抢鲜字幕组（人工智能翻译版）
Fresh Chinese Subtitles
我是一个寂寞的牛仔
I was a lonesome cowboy
尽可能地寂寞
Lonesome as I could be
你过来改变了我的生活
You came along and changed my life
并修复了我心碎的东西
And fixed what was broken in me
我是一个寂寞的牛仔
I was a lonesome cowboy
我没有朋友
I didn't have a friend
现在我的朋友们从我耳边传来
Now I got friends coming out of my ears
我再也不会寂寞了
I'll never be lonesome again
当你独自一人时 你不能幸福
You can't be happy when you're all by yourself
继续 告诉我 我错了？你错了
Go on, tell me I'm wrong? You're wrong
有人带你从架子上下来
When someone takes you down from the shelf
和你一起玩 这很精彩
And plays with you some It's wonderful
太棒了？我是一个寂寞的牛仔
Wonderful? I was a lonesome cowboy
但不再了
But not anymore
我刚刚发现了爱是什么
I just found out What love is about
我以前从未有过这种感觉
I've never felt this way before
我是一个寂寞的牛仔
I was a lonesome cowboy
但不再了
But not anymore
卡布！
Caboom!
是!
Yes!